Finding Aid for the Joe Menosky papers, 1983-2005, (bulk 1995-2001) LSC.2250
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Publications and Memorabilia, 1964, 1968, 1979, 1994-2002
  - Star Trek The Magazine, (2002 Oct) (Box 6)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Masks - article in psychology journal, (1994) (Box 30)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: - newspaper clippings, (1994) (Box 30)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Captain Dathon action figure (2 items), (undated) (Box 41)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Captain Dathon action figure (2 items), (undated) (Box 41)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: mousepad of Captain Picard, (undated) (Box 6)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: plaque - Riker quote, (undated) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek: Action! - book, (c. 1998) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek: Science Logs - book, (c. 1998) (Box 6)
  - Star Trek: The Magazine - Special Issue: Voyager, (2000 Oct) (Box 15)
    Special issue on Star Trek Voyager.
  - TV Guide featuring Star Trek Voyager (2 issues), (undated) (Box 14)
  - TV Guide featuring Star Trek Voyager (2 issues), (2000 March-April) (Box 16)
  - TV Guide with Star Trek Voyager featured on the covers (3 issues), (2001 May) (Box 16)
  - TV Guide Official Collector's Edition - Star Trek: 30 Years, (c. 1996) (Box 6)
  - Utne Ur Reader, (1998 Feb) (Box 18)
    Star Trek featured on the cover.
  - Vision of the Future: Star Trek Voyager (A) - book, (c. 1998) (Box 6)
  - Voyage Continues: Trek, the Next Generation (The) - book, (ca. 1992) (Box 40)
  - Yahoo! Internet Life magazine, (1996 Dec) (Box 18)
    Star Trek special issue.
  - Yahoo! Internet Life science fiction star map, (undated) (Box 33)